Harrison Weisberg

Software Engineer

845.641.0864 | hpweisberg@gmail.com | Los Angeles, CA | linkedin.com/in/harrisonweisberg | harrisonweisberg.com | github.com/hpweisberg

#### **SUMMARY**

Software engineer & strategist with 7+ years of experience in brand management, data analysis, business development & customer success. Skilled in crafting creative, automated solutions for corporate processes while holistically addressing client, company, team, & product needs.

#### SKILLS & TECHNOLOGIES

**Experienced:** JavaScript ES6+, Node.js, Express, React, Redux, Relational Databases, NoSQL Databases, Git, GitHub, Webpack, OOP, Functional Programming, RESTful APIs, MVC Framework, Material UI, HTM, CSS, Agile Methodologies **Working Knowledge:** TypeScript, Python, Azure, Docker, Test Driven Development (TDD), MongoDB, Mongoose, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, AJAX, OAuth, JWT, Postman, Python, Bootstrap, Figma, Photoshop, & other Adobe products

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Chores for Coins | Hackathon Winner | Software Engineer

2023

- Engineered server & NoSQL database for seamless integration of three models
- Implemented secure JWT authorization, ensuring privacy for parents & children
- Tailored React components to match UI/UX designs with pinpoint accuracy matching 95% of the original design
- Arranged daily Scrum sessions to secure strong functionality between developers, designers, & hackathon staff
- Identified three top pain points among parents, leading to the creation of the app
- Led a 10-minute stage demo, presenting to judges while showcasing functionality, & fielding questions

# **Mamba** | Snake Game | Software Engineer

2022

- Developed game board capable of handling 256 objects, optimizing placement & increasing speed by 300%
- Crafted responsive design without frameworks, enhancing theme without compromising gameplay, increasing
  accessibility compatibility by 25%
- Conducted QA testing, improving user experience & playability, increasing playtime by 80%

### **Cast** | CRM Database for Casting Directors & Talent | Software Engineer

2023

- Employed React Router to harness lazy loading & page routing to optimize performance speed by 3%
- Developed a universal search component to optimize database querying by increasing performance speed by 5%
- Streamlined Express middleware, ensuring RESTful architecture & improving server request/response by 6%
- Established git workflow, reviewing 8-10 pull requests daily for code quality & consistency on a 3-person team

### **Meltwater** | Key Account Manager

2022 - 2022

- Managed 50+ client relationships for a SasS company, including Lime, Docker, & Turo
- Collaborated with clients to boost campaign performance & social media presence by 60%
- Created & refined boolean searches, leading to a 35% increase in relevant results & mentions
- Automated performance reporting, with campaign-specific insights, resulting in boardroom-ready presentations

### **Nielsen** | Sports Account Manager

2021 - 2022

- Conducted data analysis utilizing proprietary tools for 25+ clients including Nike, Comcast, P&G, Oakley
- Provided insight & strategy for clients, improving brand recognition & increasing ROI on an average of 40% YoY
- Harnessed live game data to pitch design choices, such as Oakley's NFL helmet, increasing brand recognition by 60%
- Mentored & supervised a 4-person team, emphasizing learning & development

# William Morris Endeavor | PR Account Coordinator

2019 - 2020

- Orchestrated local & national marketing efforts, yielding a 50% increase in brand placements
- Recieved PRWeekly's Best Integrated Campaign award in 2020 led the virtual pivot of USAA's Memorial Day event
- Secured celebrity & athlete partnerships, generating 90 million+ social impressions for Ubisoft's activations
- Coordinated XFL launch, organizing stakeholder interviews & surpassing target impressions by 120%

# **EDUCATION**

Certificate | Software Engineering | General Assembly

2023

Bachelor's Degree | Film, Television, & Interactive Media | Computer Information Systems | Quinnipiac University

2016